You've got to fill out your team roster.
Our party organizer needs it.
You each get to participate twice.
And once you've picked your lineup, it's set in stove.
It's got the events listed.
Race, ballgame, and the team contest.
What's that say?
Well, looks like we can all take part in the race.
Three for the ballgame, and then five of us for the team contest.
Cool.
You can go ahead and sign me up for all three.
No, can't do that.
The rules say that two is the limit.
Ugh, we can't lose this thing.
I just know they're going to take Captain Usopp if we do.
No, they aren't.
They're going to take me.
I'm the cute one.
And it's time to announce the rosters each team has chosen to represent them in today's events.
First up, we've got the Straw Hat Pirates.
Participating in round one, the Donut Race, is the entire Straw Hat crew.
Did I ever tell you I got a disease that prevents me from racing?
I don't want to do this stupid race either, so just man up.
Participating in round two, the groggy ring, is Roro Noa Zoro, Sanji, and Tony Tony Chopper.
You better not slow me down.
Right back at you.
I'm going to try my hardest.
And participating in round three, the Run Round Around, we've got Monkey D. Luffy, Nico Robin, Nami, and Usopp.
Aren't we supposed to have five?
We're one member short here.
Well, who cares?
Let's go!
A captain, a swordsman, a navigator, a sniper, a cook, a doctor, and an archaeologist.
So tough, but I do have to decide who it is I'm going to take.
I believe it'd be that one right there.
Yes, that is the one I want.
All right!
Let the merciless Davy back begin!
A winner will be crowned, while the loser will be forcibly drowned.
I am Itaminizu!
You may know me as the Foxy Pirates Party Organizer, but today I will be your commentator!
Our first event of the day is round one, the Donut Race!
How do you guys think we should team up?
Hmm.
Considering that some of us have devil fruit powers, it makes sense to split into two teams of three and four people.
Legal votes for the Donut Race can only be constructed from two oars and three empty barrels.
You will be disqualified if you use any other materials.
This is the perfect chance for shipwrights to show up!
If you left your empty barrels at home, come on up here and get some!
All for free!
Because that's how generous we are!
I'm not entirely sure if three barrels is enough material to build a boat big enough to hold all four of us.
Right.
We better go with three teams, insisting of...
What the hell?
You can't just bust them up like that!
Sure I can't!
Just watch!
I am going to make us a killer boat!
All right, I'll take this time while everyone's preparing to explain how the race works.
The course consists of one lap around Long Ring Long Land.
It may sound easy, but believe me, it's not.
If your boat sinks, your team is immediately disqualified from the race.
Oh yeah, weapons, they're allowed!
Guns, cannons, explosives, anything you can think of!
If that sounds unfair, then you've got no right at all to call yourself a pirate!
I'm kind of amazed I've finished.
And time is just about up!
I hope everyone is ready!
Ooh!
Gather round, folks!
The final odds are in!
I'll announce them in order of their popularity, starting with the most popular, of course!
Just as I thought!
The top spot goes to our idle and fellow Foxy Pirate, Porcha!
Oh, you're too kind!
Joining her is the Fishman, Kaputti!
Their vessel is the Cutie Wagon, led by the Star Shark, Mom-Nah!
Yeah!
Take him down, Porcha!
You can do it!
Hold on!
You've got a shark pulling your boat?
I didn't hear him mention any rules forbidding the use of sharks!
The second most popular team?
Well, this is certainly surprising!
It's the Skull Hat team of Navigator Nami, Sniper Usopp, and Archaeologist Robin!
Their official craft is the Barrel Tiger!
That chick with the orange hair is smokin' hot!
I am praying that the dark-haired babe joins our crew!
They can keep the guy!
Yeah, agreed!
Well, sounds like the only thing our Foxy crew cares about are the pretty girls!
What a bunch of hornballs!
You're sure this won't sink?
I told you, I am not a professional shipwright, okay?
But I know it's at least better than those abominations!
Just because it floats doesn't mean it's a boat, it's more like Flotsam!
Flotsam!
You've got to do that the whole time?
Yep!
It's a good thing I enjoy riding, huh?
It's a miracle they float!
It's all on our shoulders if our crew's gonna win this race, as usual!
And coming in first on our list is...
The Harem Nocturne!
A beautiful boat full of beautiful women in favor of beautiful people!
In fourth place, we've got the Crab Crane!
An old favorite in the top ranks!
In fifth and sixth place are the Swordfish King 1 and 2!
In seventh place is the Party Love and Pleasure Boat!
And in eighth place, the all-reliable Duke Special!
What's the deal?
You even gonna bother to mention our boat?
Same here!
What gives?
Uh...
Let's see!
Dr. Chopper and Swordsman Zorro's boat, the basically perils is...
Their boat is third to last in popularity!
Yep, I was expecting worse.
And they at least it floats, boat!
Looks like they win the booby prize!
Hey, what's a booby prize?
It means our boat is second to last.
There can't seriously be a boat worse than theirs!
Coming in last on the list of popularity...
We've got the giant barge, the Behemoth Mothership Coaster!
You're kidding me.
The oars can't be long enough for that thing.
How are they supposed to see it?
Yeah, you guys are sharp.
You're right about the oars, though.
Way too short.
And the damn thing is filled with seawater, too!
Not fair!
Those jerks!
Boy, no way that thing is just three barrels.
Sure it is!
We pieced together the three biggest barrels we could find.
There ain't nothing in the rule book about how small your barrel's gotta be.
Okay, all of the boats are now at the starting line!
I'll continue to provide commentary throughout the race with a bird's eye view of the action
from atop Chirp Chirp, a rare South Blue Super Sparrow!
Ah, Chirp Chirp!
There you go, what's up?
Yeah, drown that long nose!
Who, me?
That's it!
We have to win this now!
Drowning is fair play.
It's in the rules.
Wow, they think they have a chance of winning!
Let the fools think whatever they want to think, Porcha.
We'll sink them right off the bat.
Right, Monda?
Hey!
I'm excited about this!
What?
About losing?
Now pay close attention, Usopp.
If anything happens to those two ladies, I'll eviscerate you.
We are gonna win this race!
I know it!
Fool!
He honestly thinks they're gonna win!
What a riot!
No one's ever beat the Foxy Pirates!
I doubt this race will even last five minutes.
Am I right?
P-p-p-p-p.
You know it.
I know it.
To ensure you don't get lost, we're providing each team with an eternal pose!
Get lost?
Try not to wander too far from the island's coast!
What's this doofus talking about?
Why would we leave the island?
We're taking the inside track the whole way!
I'm afraid it won't be that simple.
What?
Why not?
Take a look.
Excluding the big one in the back, all the other boats are on the outside track facing
out to sea.
It's a little suspicious.
Now!
On your marks!
Get ready!
Just tell me why it won't be simple!
Trust me.
Hey, listen up!
Get away from the shoreline as soon as the race starts!
Huh?
What did he say?
Yeah!
Tell me why!
Scheme!
I've got a terrible feeling about this!
No, quit babbling and tell us why already!
Push it!
Time to reveal the secret of our book.
It's got a sneaky little purpose.
Huh?
What's with the barrels?
No!
We didn't get far enough!
What's the big deal?
It's just a barrel.
No, not me!
Don't!
And they've been released!
Look at that!
Kaboom!
The old barrel mines!
The Coaster's Chump Card!
See you later, chumps!
You're supposed to avoid sinking, you know!
Wish us good luck!
Go away!
Dumb bombs!
I'll knock them all back!
Now gum gum!
Cut it out, Luffy!
Stop!
Are you trying to blow us out of the water?
Calm down!
You gotta do something!
Yeah, but that something can't involve touching them!
Luffy, pass that oar over here!
Huh?
What are you doing, Zoro?
Stand back and watch!
Huh?
What are you doing, Zoro?
Stand back and watch!
Whoa!
They're coming back this way!
It's a mighty hand to the white car!
What am I holding up with the wall right here?
Oh, they're coming back this way!
Oh, crap.
Nami! Robin, look!
Hit the deck and hold on tight!
We gotta ride this wave!
We can't ride this!
We can't ride this wave!
Yahoo! This is awesome!
Dammit, she's starting to break up on us!
This is terrifying!
Man, that's cold.
Not good!
I can't believe it!
The Straw Hat team is zipping their way to the front of the race!
This is incredible, folks!
What the?
No way! They're about to catch up with us!
Let's go, Monda!
Put every ounce of strength into it!
Hey, you guys!
We could really use some mega!
Shit!
Bye!
It's finally dying down!
Oh, man.
That didn't exactly leave the raft in the best condition.
Oh, boy! That was awesome!
I hope something causes another wave, right?
Shut up!
Another wave will flatten this lame boat you built!
I just hope the girls are okay.
There they are!
You guys looking for a party?
Well, hello there, gentlemen!
Ow!
What the?
Whoa!
Hey, relax, guys.
This is a friendly visit.
All right!
Hope you like fish and noodles!
Free of charge!
For real?
How cool!
Thank you!
Why is it that all the good cooks like you were already taken?
Your curlicue eyebrows are so cute!
You know, I gotta say, I won't mind if I get Davy back!
You must be exhausted.
Not to mention hot in that fur coat.
It's not a fur coat!
Whoa!
I'm sorry!
Let me make it up to you.
Would a candy apple be a good start?
What's a candy apple?
Is it sweet?
Hey, we need another round of drinks down here!
The brew is endless, so drink all you want!
Thanks, you guys are all right!
Update!
It looks like the pleasure boat and the harem nocturne have made a move!
The party distraction!
And they've lured in two straw hat boats for the KO!
Yeah!
Ultra seconds, please!
Wow, you're really chowing down, kid!
Come on!
We're right in the middle of a race, you jerks!
You really shouldn't concern yourself with those other guys!
If I were you, I'd be more worried about my own boat right now!
All right, Capote, give him a taste of your fish man karate!
Yeah!
Surface Splitter!
The boat's breaking apart!
Nami!
Robin!
Come on!
The girls need our help!
Let's go!
Chopper, let's move!
Huh?
Don't worry, Nami!
We're coming, Robin!
Hey!
Get back here!
We're coming, Robin!
We'll never forget your twirly eyebrows!
Our balance!
We've gotta stay balanced!
Take this!
Eat flame!
No thanks!
All right.
Ocho!
What the?
Capote!
And now, flip!
Perfect!
Now's our chance!
Usak, jump in the water and pull the boat!
Hurry!
Are you crazy?!
Capote!
Moja!
Get it together!
Come on!
Pedal!
All right, folks!
Currently in the lead of the race is everyone's all-time favorite, the Cutie Wagon!
Right behind them in second place is the Barrel Tiger, followed by...
Wow!
Guess they're back in the running!
Third place is the Crab Crane!
Okay.
I think it's about time that we get to work, Hamburg.
Really?
Oh boy, I was hoping you'd say that.
Nami!
Robin!
Just hang tight!
I'm gonna save you!
I just had the best idea ever!
Hey, Sanji!
Throw me that board!
This is really fast!
I know, right?
I'm on my way!
Just hold on, ladies!
We're getting nowhere here.
I'm pretty sure it'd be faster if we paddled.
Yeah, well, the thing is, I used the oars to build this handle.
What?
Not even a hello, huh?
Not our style.
We believe in winning any way we can.
Really?
Well, in that case...
Bull Needle!
Zoro!
Damn!
If we're going down, we're taking you with us!
Chopper!
Look out!
The basic ring barrels and the Zordfish King boats have been sunk!
They're officially disqualified!
Are you okay?
That really stuck!
Thank you, Zoro!
You hear that?
They're out of the race!
Which means we're our only hope.
Hey, wait a sec!
Why don't we just use one of your dials?
Oh!
Good idea!
We can give this breath dial a shot!
We were going faster before!
Ugh!
Don't tell me we used up all of the wind while escaping from Navarone!
Well, do you have a jet dial on you?
Come on!
You know how rare those are!
Why not use an impact dial?
Uh...
Gee, you know, I think I must have left it back on the Mary.
What?
You don't believe me?
Oh, come on!
Do you genuinely think I would lie about something this important?
We're talking about losing a crew member!
I didn't say anything.
He's right!
We can't lose here!
There's just too much at stake!
If we lose, I know they'll definitely take me first!
I just know it!
Oh, why?
Why am I so cute?
Whatever.
You just keep on dreaming.
Robin!
This isn't the best time for reading!
I'm rowing, too.
Well, yeah, your hands are, but you're not really focused on it.
Right, Robin.
You don't want to end up like me, right?
Better work hard.
I am working hard.
Yeah, working hard in archaeology.
What do you think?
Should we head for the finish line?
Or should we enjoy seeking them first?
I enjoy casually scrolling through the finish line as much as the next guy, but I want to make that chick suffer.
Simply winning this thing ain't gonna be enough for me anymore.
And the race has officially entered its climactic moments!
The cutie wagon is holding on to its lead spot, but the barrel tiger is right behind him, and the crab crane's maintaining its spot in third!
What the hell?
Where did the crab crane go?
Oh, there it is!
Geez!
Yeah, those guys had some pretty crazy moves.
Unbelievable, folks!
The crab crane's officially out of the race!
But I don't know how...
What's that?
Huh?
Whoa!
Fancy meeting you here!
See ya, chops!
What?
How are they even going so fast?
Ugh, no more strength.
Huh?
They stopped.
Brinkum screw.
Fast but no fast no more.
Sleep now.
I think he's given it all he's got.
Hey!
We better get to paddling before we lose our edge!
Thanks for handing first place to us!
Oh, man!
And we just passed those guys!
And that's the last time you'll even see us!
What the?!
How's this work for ya?
Excellent, Robin!
That is downright cheating!
Let go!
It's too bad they already noticed.
Capote, no!
They're gonna pay!
Are you ready to go again?
Wolfie?
I get the feeling he's gonna be like this for quite a while.
Let's just keep paddling with all we got.
We gotta try and catch up to him before they get an even bigger lead on us!
You're right.
Let's paddle.
Well then.
I guess I'll be sinking them after all.
Cool!
Hmm?
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
They're now approaching the most fearsome obstacles of the course!
The Long Coral Reef!
And just beyond that foreboding and difficult patch is the dreaded Long Ring Whirlpool of Long Cape!
Can they overcome these hurdles?
And, oh, we'll all be!
What now?
Talk about unexpected!
It's Full Dash Hamburg at full speed!
And riding atop him is the master of obstruction himself!
The scourge of fairness and the greatest scoundrel of all time!
Our boss, Silver Fox Foxy!
It's him!
I've just come up with an evil idea.
The endcore list!
Tell us something we will never touch in the2019's Land.
Please come in and see!
그다음6
You got bad day
Interrupt me!
Silver Fox Foxy, the Merciless Interference.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!